Two rings filled with a fatal poison have
been implanted around
JoJo's neck and heart.
Neither can be removed.
Before the rings dissolve
and the poison is released,
JoJo must defeat the powerful Wamuu
in order to secure the antidote.
What was I thinking?
When I said I needed a month,
I only meant it as a bluff.
I didn't think he'd take me seriously.
I should have said I needed a year.
A tip for you, Jojo.
Quit screwing around and act like a man!
We need to think of something, and fast!
I know, this is how I think.
But there really isn't any point
in thinking about this too hard.
If we do that, we'll realize just
how much trouble we're both in here.
Once you're done with your thinking,
Freakout, I want you to pay close
attention to what I'm about to do here.
Huh?
The water's suspended in mid-air!
Jojo, catch!
Try to keep the water
in the glass like that.
Easy!
I can do that, no sweat!
Here's what you did wrong.
The strength of your hamon is
pretty much equivalent to mine.
But you waste a lot of your power because
you release it from the palm of your hand.
And thus, you can't
control the water. However,
when I hold the water, I release Hormone
from the tip of one of my fingers,
a single point.
That method allows me to focus my energy,
making it easy to control the water.
Scattering Hormone everywhere the way
you do just disperses your energy.
Think of it like using
a squirt gun with its
smaller hole rather
than an open water hose,
capiche?
You're naturally gifted, Jojo,
but you need a lot of work to
get your Hamon under control.
I brought you to Venice to meet my
mentor, but it's gonna be a grind.
Oh no!
Grind and work are probably my two least
favorite words in the English language.
Thank
you
so
much for watching.
Thank you.
I want to be with the world.
I'll see you in the dark.
I'll see you
in
the
dark.
The world is so far.
doing in a place like this?
Excuse me.
Do you know Air Saplina Island and
how long it takes to get there?
Gondolier, did you hear me?
Oh, how is he standing
on that oar like that?
I don't think I like this, not one bit.
The hell?
You asked for it.
I have no idea who you are, but
I'm going to make you pay for that.
You're going to wish you never met me.
At least he can control his Hamon
well enough to stand on water.
That's a start.
A woman?
Is that you, coach?
She goes by the name of Lisa Lisa.
Nobody knows her true
name, her place of origin,
where she studied, or how she
mastered the art of Hamon.
She will be JoJo's coach for as long as
it takes, or at least for the next month.
Well, well.
Don't think that I'll forgive you for
hitting me in the face with that oar.
Just because you're a girl doesn't mean
that I won't give you what you deserve.
You should just be happy that you impressed
me with your initial display of skills.
Walking on water when you obviously lack
proper training is quite an accomplishment.
However, if you truly wish
to master Hormone in a month,
you must be prepared to die for it!
See?
She's using the oar as a high bar!
What is this?
Joseph Joestar.
From this moment forward, you will be
wearing that breathing correction apparatus.
until I say otherwise.
I can't breathe!
Not without proper rhythm, you can't.
However, with proper breath
control, you'll have no problem.
If you do not maintain proper
breath control, then yes,
the mask will eventually
suffocate you. So, focus.
Learn to master your breath and you'll
be running marathons while wearing it.
Are you crazy?
Get this damn thing off my face right...
I can't breathe!
You do realize your
training has already begun.
You can take the mask off for meals and
whenever you need to brush your teeth.
Jojo, don't make it hard on yourself.
Just keep your rhythm and
pretend that it's Halloween.
I'm gonna get you, lady.
And one more thing before I forget.
So we're both on the same page.
I did not accept the
responsibility of training
you just so that you
can save your own skin.
I am forging a squad of warriors
capable of annihilating our enemies.
You witch!
Careful.
You want another Grand with her?
I would never hit a woman.
It's always a pleasure, Caesar.
And you, Jojo.
Welcome to Venice.
Shuichi.
It can't help but respect
her harmon skills.
But good luck finding anyone
who would ever marry her.
Even if she is kinda cute.
Bow when she leaves.
Are you kidding me?
Italy's most transparent playboy wants
me to be polite to that little witch.
Watch your tongue, Jojo.
I respect her like my own mother.
She'll have the same respect.
I'm warning you.
Air Saplina Island is about 30
minutes northeast of Venice by boat.
Its mysterious air is a stark
contrast to the city of canals.
But it possesses a dark beauty that
seems to be a perfect fit for Lisa Lisa.
This is your new training ground, Jojo.
I have claimed that
entire island as my home.
So this is where I'll have
to die for my Hamon training.
We'll just see about that.
So I see, I'm glad you're
safe and my grandson too.
I don't know if I've ever been happier.
Hey, if you mention one word about
those stupid poison rings to granny,
I'll beat you senseless.
It would do no good to tell her anything.
No sense wasting any more of my time.
I hope you're ready for the
hell climb pillar. Wait.
Seriously, what's the big deal?
But but coach,
you know that I haven't even made an
attempt on hell climb pillar right?
Do you really intend
for us to start on this?
So many have died on hell climb pillar.
I've heard countless stories.
Stories that may or may not be true.
If you fail, you have no place here.
Hello?
Would somebody care to clue
me in on what's going on?
This hell pillar thing doesn't
really look all that tall.
Well, from up here, it's
really more deep than tall.
Go to it.
Please don't do this.
What the hell is this?
Oh yeah, this pillar is
covered in flowing oil.
It's 24 meters to the top of the pillar
and you may only use your hands to climb.
There is no other way out.
If you can't find a way to climb
back, you'll die down there.
But that's impossible!
There's no way that anyone
could climb up that pillar!
JoJo and Caesar must now overcome the most
grueling of all Hamon endurance tests,
the Hell Climb Pillar.
This is really bad.
I can barely cling to the pillar,
and moving my fingers even a
little bit is so exhausting.
If I were to fall now, I wouldn't have
anything left to start climbing again,
but I can't think like that right now.
Otherwise, Jojo and I will
both starve to death down here.
Jojo!
The longer you stay in that muck,
the harder it is to climb out.
Now focus!
No!
I must stay focused on myself.
I can't get distracted,
not even for a second.
This is ridiculous!
I just got here!
That smug witch knows I'm not
strong enough to climb this stupid,
stupid, stupid, stupid thing!
It's not fair!
Just who the hell does she think she
is anyway, throwing us down this hole?
There's no way I could possibly
respect her after this!
I've always been patient
when it comes to women,
but she'd better start praying that
I never make it out of here alive!
Bloody hell!
So this idiotic pillar claimed the lives
of a lot of trainees is that right?
Maybe they were all just too dimwitted
to come up with a creative solution!
Using anything but hormone
is an insult to the
pillar and your training
the hell climb pillar.
Lisa only accepts Hormone.
It refuses anything else.
So don't ever forget that.
Wait a sec, come back, Lisa-Lisa!
I mean, coach, wait!
You wouldn't really leave
me down here to rot?
Just because I don't have enough power!
to climb out of here, would you?
I mean, it's my first day.
This is just some kind of test, right?
To teach me humility?
You'll pull me out later, right?
Right?
Huh?
Her eyes are like ice.
She really means it.
She's just going to let me die down here.
Curse her!
What gives her the right to do this?
The fact that she's so
damn beautiful just makes
me even more furious
about this whole thing!
28 hours later, Caesar is at 15
meters, while Jojo is at 0 meters.
The rings will now dissolve in 28 days.
I'm pretty sure we've
been in here overnight,
and Caesar still has a long
way to go up that pillar.
I should be focusing on myself, but I
can tell that he's really struggling.
His fingers look like
they're about to come loose.
If he loses that grip, he's
going to come sliding down.
His hormone looks like
it's about to run out.
Caesar, focus!
Oh, he looks like he's
about to fall again.
He's hanging by his fingertips. Caesar!
Oh, wait a second.
Is that how he's been
climbing this entire time?
By using just his fingertips like that?
He wasn't about to fall off at all.
He was just...
Think of it like using a squirt
gun with its smaller hole.
That's...
that's it!
It totally makes sense now!
Consider this hormone mystery solved!
Let's see how this works!
I did it! It's working!
My hormone is sticking to the pillar!
All this time I had my hands flat.
I was trying to use them
to support my weight,
when in fact it's the opposite that works.
Focused Hamon concentrated into the
fingertips is where the true strength lies.
What a simple little trick.
I've got it now.
All I have to do from
here on up is just climb.
And plot my revenge on
that so-called Hamon coach.
JoJo's got it. Good for him.
Another 24 hours have passed.
Caesar is now at 18 meters.
And JoJo is at 16 meters.
The rings will dissolve
in exactly 27 days.
Oh, boy.
Now I can see why Caesar started to slow
down so much once he got to this point.
The pillar begins curving
outward here as it goes up.
This is where things
are going to get tough.
The pillar is as unforgiving
as that damn Lisa Lisa.
It is now, three hours later.
Caesar is at 19 meters.
Jojo at 18 meters.
Oh, is that a...
Yes, it is. It's a crack.
And it should be just big
enough for my fingers.
Thank goodness.
Time for a well-earned break here.
I can't believe my luck.
Things are finally
starting to look up for me.
Oh, no! What was that?
It felt like some kind of switch.
Did you feel that, Jojo?
What's going on? What the? Oh, no.
The Hellclimb Pillar only accepts Hormone.
It refuses anything else.
Watch out!
What?
Something's happening!
Not good.
I must have tripped
some sort of booby trap.
This just went from
difficult to impossible.
How in the world are we supposed
to scale this thing now?
An impenetrable sheet of oil shoots
out of the pillar at a deadly speed,
near the 20-meter mark.
That stream is so highly pressurized
that it can cut like a razor!
What?
Stop looking at me like that!
It was an accident!
You can't be mad at me!
Look, I'm sorry, okay?
I was just trying to rest for a second.
I did what any other sane
person would have done.
Whatever madman designed this
diabolical thing, set that up as a trap.
I wasn't giving you a look of blame, Jojo.
I was giving you one of concern.
I'm not even sure if
I can focus my hormone
enough to get through
that oil in one piece.
There is one way up!
Whoa, what the?
He's sticking to the pillow with his feet!
Caesar!
Harmon to attract and repel!
My Harmon is now focused through
my feet to keep me on the
pillar and in my hands to protect
me as I break through the oil!
I must stay focused to control the two
opposing types of Harmon simultaneously!
I did it!
I hate to say it,
but Jojo isn't even close to being able
to control two types of Hamon at once.
There's no way he can get through that.
That was amazing.
I'm glad Caesar was able to find
his way through the oil somehow,
but there's no way I can pull
off a Hamon stunt like that.
Nine hours later.
He's done it.
Caesar reaches the top after 61 hours.
Please, coach.
Jojo can't make it through that.
You've got to turn off the oil for him.
The man has no patience at all.
He'll undoubtedly try some stupid
Tarot stunt any second now.
And he'll fail.
Well, I know that hanging around
like this won't get me anywhere.
You've got to turn that oil off.
If he tries to break through it, the
oil will end up cutting him in half.
And even if he's just
blasted to the ground,
he'll end up starving to death down there.
Coach, please!
To hell with it!
I'll make it or die trying!
Here goes nothing!
Jojo, don't!
Just stay right where you are!
I can use the strength of my
Hormone to get me out of this, too!
Jojo!
Look at that!
I don't believe it!
He's using his Hormone to slide
along the plane of the oil sheet!
The oil loses its speed
the farther it shoots out!
I'll have to launch from here!
He actually used the momentum of the oil
to whip himself up and over the top of it.
He didn't fall.
In fact, it looks like he made
it up a whole three meters.
I've never seen anyone ascend the
hell climb pillar like that before.
He did it by turning his weakness
into a strength that was quite clever.
I made it, kind of anyway.
I'm on the wall, but it's not over yet.
This overhang here is even worse than the
one that was on the pillar down below.
I don't have anything left.
I've just got one more
meter to go. Damn it!
I can't control my breathing any longer.
I'm slipping. No!
Caesar!
Let me set the record straight.
I was not mad at you earlier, Jojo.
I'm sorry, forgive me, coach, but I just
couldn't let Jojo go down like that.
I suppose I understand,
Caesar, although I'm surprised you
have any strength left yourself.
Oh, I forgot!
I could really use your other arm here!
Don't let me go!
Caesar!
Ten seconds later, and after saying
don't let me go another 13 times,
Jojo reaches the top.
Hello again, coach.
I bet you thought I was done for, huh?
I want you to know that while I was
clinging to that pillar for dear life,
I had time to think to myself,
How should I exact my
revenge upon that witch?
Should I challenge her to a duel?
Or maybe I should just squeeze
her nose until she cries?
That's interesting.
I didn't think Jojo would be the type
that would hold a grudge like that.
So which will it be, coach?
Huh?
I'm doing it.
I'm really doing it.
I'm holding the water in the
cup when it's upside down.
That's great.
In only three excruciating days,
he's improved his hormone control.
Jojo's inherent talent is incredible,
but Coach Lisa Lisa's hormone
training is even more so.
Forgive me, coach?
Please, I'll do whatever you say!
You've got to give me more
training, I beg you, please!
You'll see what I can do.
I'll overcome anything!
Well, that was pretty quick!
I didn't think you'd be able
to hold a grudge for very long.
Oh, don't worry, Jojo!
I've got plenty more for you!
I will train you into the ground!
Thank you, coach!
Your next three weeks
here are going to make
the Hellclimb pillar look
like a cakewalk? Huh?
Who the hell do you think you
are sneaking up on me like that?
Whoa, who are these guys?
He's made the water move like pudding.
I would like for you to meet
two of my finest servants.
These men will be your new instructors.
Say hello to Machina and Logs.
I can't even imagine how to do that.
Would you like to learn, then?
Didn't you hear me ask if you
wanted to learn how to do this?
Yes, of course I did.
Learning from you would be an honor.
Well, fine then.
Come closer, take a look, and
I'll show you what's going on.
Why do you chumps want
hormone training? No matter.
From here on out, we're gonna
forge you into real men!
Strengthen your breath!
How can your muscles be strong if what
supports them is weak as a butterfly?
You must be able to take ten
full breaths in a single second!
This sucks!
You will inhale for ten minutes,
and then exhale for ten minutes!
The mask doesn't come off until then!
Really?
You guys are insane!
Seven days remain until
the rings dissolve.
Call it morning, running through the sun.
And in and out of the valley.
In and around the lake.
Moms come out of the sky.
They stand there.
While in my lover we'll be there.
We'll see you.
Don't you suppose we'll be there?
You'll be too.
24, 24, my love, you sing.
I'll be there with you.
I'm afraid it's necessary
for a final examination.
The solution is finding more power.
Deep down, he's worth having as a friend.
Horrible. Unnatural.
I just can't take it.
Thank you.